<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Naru Equiptments</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Contact Naru</string>
    <string name="about1">Established in the year 1987, Naru Kitchen Equipment is one of the ISO 9001:2008 Certified leading manufacturer, supplier and exporter of Commercial Kitchen Cooking and Refrigeration Equipment. Our equipment including display counter (csr, csh), gas deep fryer, refrigerator pizza table, blast chiller freezers are appreciated for their high efficiency, sturdy construction and less power consumption. These are widely used in restaurants, fast food centers, hotel and canteens.\n\nOur owner Mr. Suresh Rajpal has wide experience and deep knowledge in the industry. Under his excellent guidance, we have developed skilled team personnel, who assist us in all our endeavors and efforts. Along with this, our manufacturing unit with advanced machines helps us to develop our equipment with high quality standards.\n\nAs per the customer’s specifications, we offer this equipment in various size, model, dimension and height. These are packaged with quality material and delivered quickly to our customers. Owing to these reasons, we have a Product Portfolio chive. We have our huge clients from all across the globe.</string>
    <string name="about_topic2">A renowned firm, we are involve in providing heavy duty kitchen equipment, ventilation system, ducting, hoods and gas/fluid pipe lines suit to hospitality industry and allied industrial organizations. We have tied up with families group of companies, the name of which is mentioned below:\n \u2022 Pristine Metal Form Private Ltd (Vasai, Thane)\n \u2022 Gemtech (Vashi, Mumbai)\n \u2022 Lasertech (Bhayander, Thane)</string>
    <string name="about_topic3">
Our company is managed and Motivated by an efficient group mentors, they are consistently strive to make our organization number one in the industry. Their hard work and insight have helped us to achieve good reputation in the industry. Our proprietor Mr. S. N. Rajpal has a wide industrial experience of two decades. He has thorough technical knowledge and is an expert in acquiring raw materials to fabrication of end products. He also looks after Sales side.\n\nOur Technical and Sales side is controlled by Mr. S. N. Rajpal (Proprietor) and production side is controlled by Mr. S. Sawant. Our administration and accounts is managed by Mr. P. S. Rajpal, who has an industrial experience of a decade.</string>
    <string name="hometext">Welcome to Naru Equiptments\n\nWe, Naru Kitchen Equipment, are manufacturing, supplieng and exporting of Commercial Kitchen Cooking and Refrigeration Equipment. We are offering wide range of products that are fabricated using supreme quality components and other material procured from some of the trusted sources. Moreover, the complete range of products are designed, manufactured and packed with the aid of sophisticated machinery and latest technology. Our equipment including display counter (csr, csh), gas deep fryer, refrigerator pizza table, blast chiller freezers are appreciated for their high efficiency, sturdy construction and less power consumption. Our Offering products are wideley used in restaurants, fast food centers, hotels and canteens.Our offering equipment range comprises display counter (csr, csh),Gas Deep Fryer, Refrigerator Pizza Table, Blast Chiller Freezer, Work Counter, Dim Sum Trolley, Bain Marie, Tilting Soup Kettle, 4 Burner Gas, Stainless Steel Kitchen Hoods and Refrigerator Under Counter (Vertical)</string>
    <string name="aboutHead">Profile</string>
    <string name="contact">Naru Equipment\nSuresh Rajpal (Owner)\nRM 54, Khan Gully, Opposite Garuda Petrol Pump, Kandivali West\nMumbai - 400067, Maharashtra, India</string>
    <string name="project_list">\n\n\n\u2022 Jnana Prabhodini Medical Trust  Man. By Lata Mangeskar Foundation\n\n \u2022 Sahara India Commercial Corpn. Ltd. Lonavala\n\n \u2022 Raj Mudra Restaurant \u0026 Bar (Mumbai)\n\n \u2022 Ramada Hotel Manohar, (Five Star) Hyderabad\n\n \u2022 Hotel Golkonda Four Star, Hyderabad.\n\n \u2022 Manas Hotel P. Ltd. Igatpuri\n\n \u2022 Hotel K. K. International 4 Star Rajkot\n\n \u2022 Natural Inn (Surat)\n\n \u2022 Hariyali Restaurant Surat\n\n \u2022 Bharat Petroleum Corpn , Mumbai\n\n \u2022 Radalt Electric Ind. Ltd\n\n \u2022 Trillion Exports for Tanzania\n\n \u2022 Mahesshwary Resort, Rajkot\n\n \u2022 TarapurAutomic Power Plant\n\n \u2022 Boisar Hotel ZAM ZAM PALACE (Hydrabad)\n\n \u2022 Hotel NEST (KACHIGUDA, HYDERABAD)\n\n \u2022 TAJ HOTELS RESORTS AND PALACES\n\n \u2022 Reliance Industries (JAMNAGAR)\n\n \u2022 Essar Oil Ltd (JAMNAGAR)\n\n \u2022 SHIV SHAGUN HOTEL (Bhayandar)\n\n \u2022 SHIV SAGAR HOTEL (GOREGOAN, MUMBAI)\n\n \u2022 Hotel Rang Sharda pvt. Ltd. (Quality Inn) Bandra.\n\n \u2022 Silent Hill Resort Pvt. Ltd.\n\n \u2022 Citadel hotel (Now Ramee Hotel) Khar.\n\n \u2022 Sun N Sand, Mumbai.\n\n \u2022 Juhu Hotel, Juhu.</string>
    <string name="about_home">Established in the year 1987, Naru Equipment is a reputed manufacturer and exporter of commercial kitchen Refrigeration \u0026 Bakery equipments. Our company is popularly specialized in manufacturing high quality commercial kitchen equipments which includes Cooking Equipments, Food Service Equipments, Kitchen Refrigeration Equipments, Cold \u0026 Dry Storage Equipments, Dish \u0026 Pot Washing Equipments, Baking Equipments, Exhaust \u0026 Fresh Air Systems. These equipment find its application in places like hotels, kitchens, club houses, hospitals, industries and catering units.</string>
</resources>
